Guide to the Stanford Shakespeare Audiovisual Recordings SC1271
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Shakespeare Company audiovisual recordings
2011-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Shakespeare Company
SC1271
.5 Linear Feet
10 optical disc(s) (dvd)
2 optical disc(s) (blu-ray)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use.
Biographical / Historical
Renowned for creating entertaining, innovative, and accessible productions, the Stanford Shakespeare Company has received highly positive reviews both locally and nationally in the London-based magazine Plays International. A student-run repertory theatre company, the Company has previously produced such Shakespearean favorites as Romeo and Juliet, The Tempest, Othello, Twelfth Night, Hamlet, and Macbeth. Our most recent productions, Much Ado About Nothing, and Lear.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audiovisual recordings of performances.
Theatre -- Study and teaching (Higher); Dramatics.; Stanford Shakespeare Company
- Performances, 2011-2015
  - Julius Caesar, 2011-02 (Box 1)
  - As You Like It, 2011-05-13 (Box 1)
  - The Taming of the Shrew, 2012-02-23 (Box 1)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 2012-05 (Box 1)
  - Othello, 2013-02 (Box 1)
  - Love's Labour's Lost, 2013-05-22 (Box 1)
  - Henry V, 2014-02-20 (Box 1)
  - The Winter's Tale, 2014-05-21 (Box 1)
  - Lear, 2015-02 (Box 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 2015-05-19 (Box 1)